spritted.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Policy

                                 Privacy Policy
The present Privacy Policy is part of the use Agreement of the site
www.spritted.com, which the user declares to have read, understood and
accepted when registering as such.
1. USE OF COOKIES
We inform you that in the site www.spritted.com, we use cookies. Cookies are
small, electronic data files which are sent by the website to your browser and
are stored in your system’s hard drive, and are used to determine your
preferences when connecting to the services of our websites, as well as
tracking determined behaviors or activities carried out by yourself inside our
websites.
In some sections of our website, we require the client to have the cookies
enabled given that some of the featured require them to work, but under no
circumstances collect personal information (identification, contact, work
related, or in any other way).
The information obtained shall not be communicated to third parties, with the
exception of cases where possible fraudulent activities are being investigated.
If the user wants to disable the cookies, he/she must do it directly from the
web browser.
© Toro Games S.L. 2015 – All rights reserved

2. PERSONAL INFORMATION
The Register section of the website www.spritted.com contains an online
form, for which the user is required to provide a valid email address.
Said information is stored in a safe online file property of TORO GAMES to be
able to provide the services to the users, properly inscribed in the AEPD and
entrusted to a specialized company in virtue of specific contract. The
information stored in said file will only be notified to those companies
associated to TORO GAMES which participate in the provision of services
(game headlines, content suppliers, payment method providers, and so on).
The user of said form implicitly accepts said storage, treatment and
communication, but can change opinion at any moment requesting the
deletion or correction of the personal information sending an email to
info@spritted.com.
3. CHANGES IN THE PRIVACY POLICY
The present Privacy Policy may be subject to changes in the future. In said
case, the users will be appropriately informed and their consent will be
requested once again. In case of not granting it, the Agreement which
includes it shall be understood to be resolved.
© Toro Games S.L. 2015 – All rights reserved
